have to buy compute
to serve all that
revenue And you don't
want to buy too
much because you could
financially overextend yourself and
you don't want to
buy too little because
then you can't serve
all the revenue And
so that's where the
kind of economic and
financial is So but
you are involved in
that building data centers
you're vast fortunes there
you've got the deals
with NVIDIA Do you
worry that that's going
to come back and
you So we have
some advantages in this
There's a stability to
business that there is
not to consumer right
Consumer is very fickle
Enterprise purchasing predictions are
predictable Also enterprise tends
to have better margins
The margin is basically
how much buffer you
have between buying too
little and buying too
much what you have
to pay for and
what you have to
support in revenue so
we have a of
here but I won't
deny that there is
some inherent risk in
all of the to
this process Whenever you
have an upside whose
amount is uncertain or
even whose timing is
uncertain and you have
to make financial decisions
somewhat blind to those
things have to decide
early to
build out capital to
out resources a few
years in advance there's
going to be some
inherent risk that's by
that uncertainty And I
do think that some
companies have probably overbought
I'm not able to
look at their financials
I just know